Sometimes all you need is for everything to go wrong.
Luck is a animation, adventure, comedy film directed by Peggy Holmes.
Suddenly finding herself in the never-before-seen Land of Luck, the unluckiest person in the
world must unite with the magical creatures there to turn her luck around.
Sam (voice), played by Eva Noblezada.
Bob (voice), played by Simon Pegg.
Dragon (voice), played by Jane Fonda.
Captain (voice), played by Whoopi Goldberg.
Gerry (voice), played by Colin O'Donoghue.
Marvin (voice), played by Lil Rel Howery.
Luck is a 2022 American animated fantasy comedy film directed by Peggy Holmes from a screenplay written by Kiel Murray, and a story conceived by Murray and
the writing team of Jonathan Aibel and Glenn Berger, based on an original concept created by Rebeca Carrasco, Juan De Dios, and Julián Romero.
Produced by Skydance Animation, the film features the voices of Eva Noblezada, Simon Pegg, Jane Fonda,
Whoopi Goldberg, Flula Borg, Lil Rel Howery, Colin O'Donoghue, and John Ratzenberger.
Set in the Land of Luck, the story follows the unluckiest person, Sam Greenfield (Noblezada), as
she must unite with a talking black cat named Bob (Pegg) to turn her luck around.
The project was announced in July 2017, shortly after Skydance Animation was formed on March
16, 2017, with Paramount Pictures distributing as the schedule for March 2021.
Alessandro Carloni signed on to direct the film
from a script by Aibel and Berger.
The film underwent many changes during production, such as rewrites, directors, and release dates,
and Holmes was later announced as the new director in January 2020, replacing Carloni.
Much of the main voice cast, including Noblezada and Pegg, signed on in January 2022,
following the casting of Fonda and Goldberg in February and June 2021, respectively.
Production was done remotely during the COVID-19 pandemic.
Luck premiered in Madrid on August 2, 2022, and was released on Apple TV+
and in select theaters in the United States on August 5.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of superstition, bad luck,
leprechaun, computer animation, female protagonist.
The tone is lighthearted.